(
"ai_sub_version": "1.11.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
【チラ見せ】hololive 3rd Generation Live
きゅるるん大作戦〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
[Sneak Peek] hololive 3rd Generation Live
Operation Kyururun: The Ultimate Idols, You Have to Stan Them!
【DAY1】
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[DAY 1]
The concert will be starting soon
Attention
ご来場のお客様へ
To all attendees
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
2次販売グッズ
グッズ販売期間 1.14 20:00 - 2.24 18:00
Secondary Sale Merchandise
Sales Period: Jan 14, 20:00 - Feb 24, 18:00
応援セット / 推しマフラータオル / リストバンド
Support Set / Oshi Muffler Towel / Wristband
ペンライト / Tシャツ
ペンライトカバー / ランダム缶バッジ
Penlight / T-shirt
Penlight Cover / Random Can Badge
アクリルスタンド / モチーフストラップ / リュック
Acrylic Stand / Motif Strap / Backpack
NEW アクリルパネル
3期生からの複製直筆コメント入り！
NEW Acrylic Panel
Featuring printed handwritten comments from the 3rd Gen!
3期生のみんなを応援しています！
たくさんのメッセージありがとうございます！
We're supporting all the 3rd Gen members!
Thank you for all the messages!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
声出し応援OKです
Attention to all visitors:
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
Cheering loudly is OK.
2次販売グッズ
2nd round of merchandise sales
たくさんの素敵なショート動画ありがとうございました！
Thank you for so many wonderful short videos!
君のこと 大好き大好き大好き大好き 大好き
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you!
溢れるこの愛 きっと もっと 止まらない
This overflowing love surely won't stop, more and more
ぜひ「あいあいあいらぶゆー」のハッシュタグをつけて、たくさん投稿してね！
Please post many videos with the hashtag #AiaiaiILoveYou!
アイアイアイアイ アイラブユー
I-I-I-I I love you
君も アイアイアイアイ アイニージュ
You too, I-I-I-I I need you
もっと もっと 好きになって
Fall in love with me more and more
好きなだけ愛させて
Let me love you as much as I want
揺れるハンドがぴょんぴょんぴょん
Waving hands go boing-boing-boing
穴に落ちてあみゃあみゃ
Falling into the rabbit hole, amya-amya
こんなになっても今だ抜け出せない
Even like this, I still can't get out
どうしたもんかのぬいぬいぬい
What should I do? Nui-nui-nui
助けてきみたちあほいほい
Help me, you guys! Ahoy-hoy!
まった まった まった まった
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
好きなだけ愛してね
Please love me as much as you want
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
ぜひ『あいあいあい♡あいらぶゆー』を使って動画を作ってみてください！
Please try making a video using 'Ai Ai Ai ♡ I Love You'!
きゅるるん大作戦〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
Operation Kyururun: The Strongest Idols, You Can't Help But Support Them
〜応援メッセージ、ありがとうございます！！〜
~Thank you for your messages of support!!~
きゅるるん大作戦〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
開演までしばらくお待ちください
Operation Kyururun: The Strongest Idols, You Can't Help But Support Them
The concert will be starting soon
スクリーンの撮影・録画、SNSへのアップロードは固くお断りいたします
Screenshotting and sharing to social media is strictly prohibited
Sponsors 協賛
Sponsors
アニメにハマって歌いたくなっちゃった。
I got into anime and really wanted to sing.
推しのシーン見ながらカラオケ歌えるなんて...
To think I can sing karaoke while watching my favorite scenes...
尊すぎてツライっ！
It's so precious it hurts!
歌いたいアニメ・ゲームソング見つけよう！
Let's find the anime and game songs you want to sing!
JOYSOUND
全国のアミューズメント施設にてホロライブ３期生プライズ順次展開中！
Hololive 3rd Generation prizes are now being rolled out at amusement facilities nationwide!
全国のアミューズメント施設でGETしてね！
Get them at amusement facilities nationwide!
吉野家でごはんでしょ♪
Let's have a meal at Yoshinoya♪
ぎゅう
Beef
ぎゅう、ぎゅうぎゅう
Beef, beef beef
ぎゅう
Beef
んまっ！
Yum!
元祖の本気、召し上がれ。牛丼は吉野家。
Enjoy the dedication of the original. Yoshinoya is for beef bowls.
やっぱこれな。
This is definitely it.
ホロライブ３期生ミニCDコレクション
Hololive 3rd Generation Mini CD Collection
きゅるるん大作戦を応援しています！
Supporting Operation Kyu-ru-run!
きゅるるん大作戦
〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
Operation Kyururun
—The Ultimate Idols, You Have to Stan!—
せーの！
Ready, set...
本日は、
Today,
hololive 3rd Generation Live
きゅるるん大作戦
Operation Kyururun
〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
—The Ultimate Idols, You Have to Stan!—
にご来場いただき...
thank you for joining us...
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内をさせていただきます。
To ensure everyone enjoys the live until the end, we have a few announcements.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, audio recording, and the use of video recording equipment during the performance are strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。喫煙はご遠慮ください。
Smoking is prohibited inside the venue. Please refrain from smoking.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は無理をせず、近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
If you happen to feel unwell, please do not push yourself and inform a nearby staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、他のみんなの迷惑になったり公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
Moshing, diving, throwing objects onto the stage, or any other acts that cause trouble for others or interfere with the performance are strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
Please follow the rules and have a great time!
はーい！
Yes!
また本公演は、映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合があります。
Also, for this performance, cameras for video streaming and photography are inside the venue, and audience seats may be captured.
これらの映像や写真は、プロモーション等に使用される可能性がありますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
Please be aware that these videos and photos may be used for promotions and other purposes.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは「#きゅるるん大作戦DAY1」です。
Additionally, the hashtag for the live is #KyururunDaisakusenDay1.
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてくれると嬉しいです！
We'd be happy if you could help hype it up using the hashtag!
それでは、開演までもう少しです！
Well then, it's just a little longer until the show starts!
みんなの声、たくさん聞かせてぺこー！
Let me hear your voices, peko!
それじゃあ3期生、エンジン行くか！
Alright, 3rd gen, let's fire up!
みんな今からマイクがなくなるので、静かに静かに...
Everyone, the mics will be off soon, so be quiet, be quiet...
まもなく きゅるるん大作戦
Operation Kyururun coming soon
#きゅるるん大作戦
#OperationKyururun
兎田ぺこら
Usada Pekora
不知火フレア
Shiranui Flare
白銀ノエル
Shirogane Noel
宝鐘マリン
Houshou Marine
#きゅるるん大作戦 〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
#Operation Kyururun ~The strongest idols, you have to support them~
I I I I I love you
もう I I I I I need you
I I I I I need you even more
もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more
好きなだけ愛させて
Let me love you as much as I want
さあ、いくぜライブ！いくぞー！
Come on, let's start the live! Let's go!
みんなで最高の思い出作ろうね！
Let's make the best memories together!
ズルズルな君だらけ
Everything's full of sloppy you
どうかしてるわ ねぇ、私
I must be going crazy, hey, me
心臓 ドキドキになってる 警報
My heart's pounding like a warning siren
毎日 幻覚現れて
Hallucinations appear every day
頭に花咲いちゃって
Flowers are blooming in my head
恋ってやつは 非常識ですわ
This thing called love is truly irrational
いっそ食べちゃいたい
I'd rather just eat you up
フリーズした感情
Frozen emotions
誰もが持ってる お願い
A wish that everyone has
じゅんじゅん 呪文詠唱
Chanting incantations, one by one
どどどって 急上昇
Surging up with a 'do-do-do'
これが恋なら もう後悔しないわ
If this is love, I won't regret it anymore
だから 君のこと 大好き 大好き 大好き 大好き 大好き
That's why I love you, love you, love you, love you, love you
溢れるこの愛は じっと ずっと 止まらない
This overflowing love will never, ever stop
I I I I I love you
君が I I I I I need you
I I I I I need you
もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more
好きなだけ愛させて
Let me love you as much as I want
揺れる ハートが ぴょんぴょんぴょん
My swaying heart goes 'pyon pyon pyon'
沼に落ちて あびゃびゃ
Falling into the pit with an 'abyabya'
こんなになっても 今だ 抜け出せない
Even like this, I still can't get out
どうしたもんかね ぬいぬいぬい
What should I do? Nui-nui-nui
助けて君たち アホイホイ
Help me, you guys! Ahoy-hoy
もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more
好きなだけ愛してね
Please love me as much as you want
ふわふわ 夢のお腹
Fluffy belly of a dream
君の声で 目が覚めた
I woke up to your voice
五感全部が 君のシグナル
All my five senses are signals of you
毎度 お騒がせ ごめん
Sorry for the constant trouble
キュンで壊れちゃいそうだ
I feel like I'm going to break from the 'kyun'
恋ってやつは 制御不能ですわ
This thing called love is uncontrollable
いっそ抱きしめて
I'd rather you just hug me
壊してもいいよ
It's okay to break me
誰にも 邪魔はさせない
I won't let anyone get in the way
ピチピチ感情で
With lively emotions
キラキラ急展開
A sparkling sudden development
これが運命なら もう迷わない
If this is destiny, I won't hesitate anymore
君だけが 大好き 大好き 大好き 大好き 大好き
I love only you, love you, love you, love you, love you
私のこの愛は じっと ずっと 離さない
This love of mine will never, ever let go
Be Be Be my baby
And kiss kiss kiss kiss kiss to me
もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more
私だけを見ててね
Please look only at me
もし太郎は泣いちゃうかもね
Moshitaro might end up crying
だってそんなのってないぺこじゃん
Because that's just not right, peko!
分かってるよね ダーリン
You understand, don't you, darling?
いっぱい愛を待ってます！
I'm waiting for lots of love!
ノエル もっと！ ぺこら もっと！
Noel, more! Pekora, more!
フレア もっと！ マリン もっと！
Flare, more! Marine, more!
ホロライブファンタジーを
Hololive Fantasy...
愛してるー！
I love you!
君のこと 大好き 大好き 大好き 大好き 大好き
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
溢れるこの愛は きっと ずっと 止まらない
This overflowing love surely won't ever stop
I I I I I love you 君が I I I I I need you
I-I-I-I-I love you, you are I-I-I-I-I need you
もっと もっと もっと 好きだと言わせて
Let me say I love you more, more, more
ときめくハートが ぴょん ぴょん ぴょん
My heart goes pit-a-pat, hop-hop-hop
矢に射抜かれて あびゃびゃびゃ
Struck by an arrow, I'm dazed and confused
こんなになったら魔法は解けません
Once it's like this, the magic won't break
本気になってる ぬい ぬい ぬい
I'm getting serious, Noel-Noel-Noel
行きますわよ まだ あほい ほい
Here I go, still ahoy-hoy!
もっと もっと もっと 好きなだけ愛してね
More, more, more, love me as much as you want
I I I I I love you
I-I-I-I-I love you
I I I I I need you
I-I-I-I-I need you
I I I I I love you
I-I-I-I-I love you
I I I I I need you
I-I-I-I-I need you
私たちの愛をもっと！
Take more of our love!
叫べ！のコール！
Shout! The call!
あんじゃピチピチ
I'm fresh and bouncy
あほい！
Ahoy!
ピチピチ
Bouncy-bouncy
あほい！
Ahoy!
お色気担当のマリンです
I'm Marine, the one in charge of sex appeal
ヨーソロー！
Steady as she goes!
踊るあほいに見るあほい
The dancing fool and the watching fool
共にどつら君に配りましょう
Let's hand them out to you together
お祭りだい 全長だら
It's a festival! Full speed ahead!
うさぎダメ 幸子独占
No rabbits allowed! Exclusive happiness!
最強女神 ぺこ ぺこら
The strongest goddess, Peko-Pekora!
ママ よしよしして
Mama, give me some headpats
欲張りね 横取りか 聖杯うさぎか
How greedy, stealing it? The Holy Grail rabbit?
大成功のため 初見コールも いけちゃう？
For ultimate success, can we even do the first-timer call?
きゅる きゅる きゅる きゅる アイドル
Kyuru-kyuru-kyuru-kyuru idol
自画自賛の コール
A self-praising call
お決まりの ファンサで 好き溢れちゃう
With the usual fanservice, love overflows
きゅる きゅる きゅる きゅる アイドル
Kyuru-kyuru-kyuru-kyuru idol
極めたおたげ踊る
Dancing with ultimate otagei
新規もいる 古参もいる
There are newcomers and veterans too
もはや着替えが濃くてじゃん
It's already so intense, peko!
会いたい
I want to see you
推したい
I want to support you
それなー！
Exactly!
おきまりコールで！
With the usual call!
現場でテンプレ 応援 きゅる きゅる
Standard cheering at the venue, kyuru-kyuru
ちあ ちあ
Cheer, cheer
フレ フレ
Go, go!
エルフで 褒められて 良いです
Being praised as an elf is nice
ひだり はいはい
Left, yes-yes
世界で一番 愛してる
I love you more than anyone in the world
今ならチャンネル登録 なんて無理よ
Asking to subscribe now is just impossible
ジョイ ジョイ エンジョイ
Joy, joy, enjoy
団長のノエルだぞ
I'm Captain Noel!
ゆるふわ脳筋 騎士団長
The fluffy, muscle-brained Knight Captain
孤独みたい ラップで言いたい
Like loneliness, I want to say it in a rap
ギュッ ドーン！
Gyu-don!
牛丼 いつもの大盛り
Beef bowl, the usual large serving
人参より お肉よ
More than carrots, it's meat!
私 実質 メンバー
I'm effectively a member
きゅる きゅる きゅる きゅる アイドル
Kyuru-kyuru-kyuru-kyuru idol
ハートの振り付けもコピーる
Copying the heart choreography too
可愛いとか 超えて好き こじらせちゃう
Beyond cute, I love you so much it's a problem
きゅる きゅる きゅる きゅる アイドル
Kyuru-kyuru-kyuru-kyuru idol
来世からも集める
Gathering even from the next life
エルチ組も エルセイも
Both the El-chi group and El-sei too
もはや全員推し決定じゃん
Now everyone's definitely a favorite!
響きたい
I want to resonate
乗りたい
I want to ride along
現場で全通 応援 きゅる きゅる
Attending every show at the venue, kyuru-kyuru
ちあー！☆ちあー！
Cheer! Cheer!
みんなのお頭！
Everyone's leader!
みんなの歌姫！
Everyone's songstress!
みんなの団長！
Everyone's captain!
みんなの船長！
ラブアンドピースな時も
In times of love and peace
推しが凹んだ時でも
Even when our favorites are down
トライアンドエラー重ねたい
I want to keep trying and learning
君と見たい景色があるんだ
There's a view I want to see with you
っしゃーいくぞー！
Alright, let's go!
きゅる きゅる きゅる きゅる アイドル
Kyuru-kyuru-kyuru-kyuru idol
自画自賛の コール
A self-praising call
お決まりの ファンサで 大好き！
With the usual fanservice, I love you!
一生好きだよ！
I'll love you forever!
犬好き！
I love you!
きゅる きゅる きゅる きゅる アイドル
Kyuru-kyuru-kyuru-kyuru idol
ラストまで追いかける
Chasing you until the very end
我の箱推し 存在が最強 大優勝
Supporting the whole group is the strongest, ultimate win!
きゅる きゅる きゅる きゅる アイドル
Kyuru-kyuru-kyuru-kyuru idol
永遠の愛 誓える
I can swear eternal love
単推しも 箱推しも
Both solo fans and group fans
もはや生涯オタク決定じゃん
Now a lifelong otaku is determined!
もうずっと
Forever now...
現場で限界 応援 きゅる きゅる
At the venue, cheering to the limit, kyuru-kyuru
せーの！チア！チア！
One, two! Cheer! Cheer!
一生現場で、チア！
Cheering at the scene for life!
はぁ、はぁ…やったー！
*Panting* We did it!
みんなー！
Everyone!
いぇーい！
Yay!
ちょ、ちょっと安心しすぎたぺこ。
I-I'm a bit too relieved, peko.
落ち着いて、落ち着いて。
Calm down, calm down.
落ち着くために自己紹介しようってことで。
Let's do self-introductions to calm down.
自己紹介ね、オッケー。
Self-introductions, okay.
じゃあ、ぺこらから行きますよ！
Then, Pekora will go first!
こんぺこ、こんぺこ、こんぺこ！
Konpeko, konpeko, konpeko!
ホロライブ3期生の、兎田ぺこらっ…と！
Hololive 3rd Gen's Usada Pekora... tto!
待てぺこって言わせてやれよ！
Wait, let them say "peko" too!
言いたいんだって、確かに。
They want to say it, true.
もう一回やってよ、もう一回。
Do it again, one more time.
なんて言えばいいの？ぺこらは、じゃあ。
What should I say then, for Pekora?
「こんぺこ、こんぺこ、こんぺこ」って言ったら、向こうも言いたいんだよ。
When you say "Konpeko, konpeko, konpeko," they want to say it back.
ああ、そういうことね。
Oh, I see.
じゃあ、みんなやってくれますかー？
Then, will everyone do it for me?
こんぺこ、こんぺこ、こんぺこー！
Konpeko, konpeko, konpeko!
こんぺこー！
Konpeko!
いいね！
Nice!
ホロライブ3期生の兎田ぺこらっ、と！
Hololive 3rd Gen's Usada Pekora... tto!
はい、じゃあフレアは「こんぬい」じゃなくて「はい、ダーリン」って言うから「はい、ハニー」って返してください。
Okay, so Flare will say "Hi Darling" instead of "Kon-nui," so please return with "Hi Honey."
はい、ダーリン！
Hi Darling!
はい、ハニー！
Hi Honey!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ホロライブ3期生の不知火フレアっ、と！
Hololive 3rd Gen's Shiranui Flare... tto!
じゃあ団長は「牛丼は？」って言うんで「並盛りー！」って言ってください！
Then I'll say "How's the beef bowl?" so please say "Standard size!"
牛丼は？
How's the beef bowl?
並盛りー！
Standard size!
あーい、そうだよねー！
Aye, that's right!
ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルっ、と！
Hololive 3rd Gen's Shirogane Noel... tto!
君たち！今、もしかしてフレアのこと「ハニー」って言った？
You guys! Did you just call Flare "Honey"?
言ってるー！お前らー！
They said it! You guys!
浮気だー！
It's cheating!
よろよろ。
*Staggers*
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
団長のこと忘れてしまうなんて、君たち！
To think you'd forget about me, you guys!
なんちゃって。
Just kidding.
じゃあ、普通に「Ahoy」で行きますんで「Ahoy」って言ってくださいね。
Well, I'll just go with "Ahoy," so please say "Ahoy."
Ahoy!
誰がアホや！
Who are you calling a fool!
なんちゃって。
Just kidding.
ホロライブ3期生、宝鐘海賊団船長の宝鐘マリンです！
Hololive 3rd Gen, Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Houshou Marin!
せっかくだから、みんななんかアイドル口上みたいなの、ブラッシュアップしたやつやる？
Since we're here, why don't we do those idol slogans we brushed up?
え、やろうよ！やろうよこれ！やるしかなくない？
Oh, let's do it! Let's do this! We have to, right?
そう、配信でもやった、順番で。
Yeah, the ones we did on stream, in order.
順番で行きましょう、順番で。
Let's go in order, in order.
みんな覚えてるよね？ぺこらの口上。
Everyone remembers, right? Pekora's slogan.
絶対覚えてねーぞ。
I'm sure they don't remember.
覚えてるよね？ちゃんと。覚えてる人手挙げて！
You remember, right? For sure. Raise your hand if you remember!
あ、でもそこそこ挙がってるよ！めっちゃ挙がってる！
Oh, but quite a few are raised! A lot are raised!
全然挙がってないよ。全然覚えてねーって。
Not at all. They're saying they don't remember at all.
じゃあ、今から覚えてくださいね。じゃあぺこらから行きますよ！
Well, learn it now. Then, Pekora will go first!
ラビット・キャロット・キラッと登場！最強アイドルぺこらが来たぺこ！まだまだ続くよ、ぺこらストーリー！
Rabbit, Carrot, Kiratto arrival! The strongest idol Pekora has arrived, peko! The Pekora Story continues on and on!
ちょっとフレアめっちゃ難しいんだけどさ、いけるかなこれ？
Flare's is really hard, but I wonder if we can do it?
いけるいける！みんなも掛け声、大丈夫だよ。
We can do it! Everyone knows the calls, it'll be fine.
これ、みんなにもコール＆レスポンスしてほしくて。
I want everyone to do a call & response for this.
「準備は？」って言ったら「万端！」
When I say "Ready?", say "Perfect!"
「ホールは？」って聞くので「簡単！」って言ってください。
I'll ask "The hall?", so please say "Easy!"
手拍子「パンパン！」ステップ「簡単！」
Handclaps, "clap clap!" Steps, "Easy!"
「私は？」 「フレアー！」
"I am?" "Flare!"
めっちゃ難いな。
That's really hard.
これ練習ね、覚えてください。
This is practice, so please remember it.
こんぬい！準備は？
Kon-nui! Ready?
万端！
Perfect!
ホールは？
The hall?
簡単！
Easy!
手拍子！ パンパン！
Handclaps! *Clap clap!*
ステップ？
Steps?
簡単！
Easy!
私は？
I am?
フレアー！
Flare!
ホロライブ3期生、不知火フレアです！
Hololive 3rd Gen, Shiranui Flare!
じゃあ団長はコール＆レスポンスないから、ちょっとラップします。
Well, I don't have a call & response, so I'll do a bit of rap.
目・何・質問、憩いの食べ物、答えは牛丼、おろしで飲み物、みんなの求婚、ダメダメ重婚、ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルです！
Eye, What, Question, a relaxing food, the answer is beef bowl, drinks are grated, everyone's proposal, no-no bigamy, Hololive 3rd Gen's Shirogane Noel!
エマリンは高齢なんで先に予習しましょうか。
Emarine is getting up there in years, so let's practice first.
エマリンが「マリンは」って言ったら君たちは「船長！」
When Emarine says "Marine wa," you guys say "Sencho!"
で、「君たちは」で「一番！」
And for "Kimi tachi wa," say "Ichiban!"
「我ら無敵の」「海賊団！」
"Warera muteki no" "Kaizokudan!"
で、最後に「宝鐘海賊団船長、宝鐘マリンです」って言うから、
And finally, I'll say, "Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Houshou Marine!"
そしたら問答無用で「可愛い！」って言う。分かりましたね？
Then you say "Kawaii!" without question. Got it?
ま、余裕だよね。
Well, it's a piece of cake, right?
あー素晴らしい、お返事できて丸。
Ah, wonderful. You can reply, so full marks.
じゃあ行きますよ！
Alright, let's go!
マリンはー！
Marine is—!
船長ー！
Captain—!
君たちはー！
You guys are—!
一番ー！
Number one—!
我ら無敵のー！
We are the invincible—!
海賊団ー！
Pirate crew—!
宝鐘海賊団船長、宝鐘マリンです！
Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Houshou Marine!
可愛いー！
Cute—!
いや気持ちいいんだよな、これマジで。
Man, this feels so good, seriously.
そんな可愛い？
Am I that cute?
よかったなあ、可愛いって言われてよかったなあ。
Good for you, glad you were called cute.
そんなことないけど...
That's not it...
え、でもコールアンドレスポンスね、ちょっと一発目からもうすごい難しいのやらせちゃってどうもすみませんね。
Wait, but the call-and-response, sorry for making you do something so difficult from the very beginning.
あー声が聞こえますよ、ペンライトも叩きまして。
Ah, I can hear your voices, and the penlights clicking.
さっきのさ、うちらのエンジン聞こえました？
By the way, did you hear our huddle earlier?
あ、聞こえた？聞こえた！やったー！
Oh, you heard it? You did! Yay!
ちょっとね、なんか聞こえるかなって不安だったんだよね。
I was a bit worried if it could be heard.
こっちにはね、君たちの声よく聞こえるんだけどさ、
We can hear your voices very well from here, but...
流石にマイク介さないと小さかったかなと思って。
I thought it might be too quiet without a microphone.
いや、お腹から出したから。お腹から出したけどね。
No, I shouted from the gut. Shouted from the gut, though.
あ、聞こえた？聞こえた！やったー！
Oh, you heard it? You did! Yay!
連チャン、聞こえるよ、こっちにも声聞こえてますよ。
Renzan, I can hear you. I can hear voices over here too.
衣装のことも言わなきゃ！
We have to talk about the costumes too!
一曲目から出ちゃいましたけど。突然の新衣装、可愛いでしょ？
We've been wearing them since the first song. Our sudden new costumes, they're cute, right?
ちょっとずつ違うところがあるんでね。
There are parts that are slightly different for each of us.
これぜひギュッと見てね。ぺこらは、耳に...
Please take a close look. Pekora has...
輪っかがついているぺこです！
...a ring attached to her ear, peko!
なんと発案者はノエルちゃん！
And the one who suggested it was Noel-chan!
そう、ノエル！すごいでしょ？
Yes, Noel! Isn't it great?
マリンはね、ヘッドドレスがね、ほらこんな感じで、バツバツバツバツ...
Marine's head dress, look, it's like this, with X-marks...
あー可愛い！可愛い！助かる〜。
Ah, cute! Cute! That's blissful.
ノエルちゃんはなんかポンポン付いてます。
Noel-chan has some pom-poms.
可愛い、フワフワ、ポンポン！
Cute, fluffy, pom-poms!
フレアは、頭のリボンかな？
For Flare, is it the ribbon on her head?
可愛いね。あとピアスも違いますね、みんな。靴下とか。
It's cute. And the earrings are different too, everyone. Socks and things.
そう、フレアはギャルじゃないんでね。
Yeah, Flare isn't a gyaru, you see.
私らはギャル！そう、ぺこらもギャル、ギャル！ギャルです。
We are gyarus! Yeah, Pekora is a gyaru too, gyaru! I'm a gyaru.
ちなみに...みなさん...うち等、結構めちゃめちゃ喋りすぎてるみたいで...
By the way... everyone... it seems we've been talking way too much...
あ、やばいやばい、嘘でしょ、嘘でしょ。このまま音楽しないのかいみたいな感じ。
Oh, no, no, you're kidding. Like, are we not going to play music?
スタッフさんにバチバチ言われてますけど。
The staff are telling us off.
でも、あの、ちなみに配信でね、見てる方、YouTubeで見てる方、概要欄にね、
But, um, by the way, for those watching the stream on YouTube...
配信チケットのリンクありますので、ぜひ、あの、次の曲でちょっとチラ見せは...
...the link for the streaming tickets is in the description. The "sneak peek" is...
あ、そうだ、終わりぺこなんだ。終わっちゃうので、今のうちに。
Ah, that's right, it's the end, peko. It's ending, so while you still can.
そう、まだぜひ見てほしいパートがいっぱいあるんですよ、是非ともお願いします。
Yes, there are still many parts we want you to see, so please.
お願いします！ハッシュタグ「きゅるるん大作戦DAY1」でいっぱい呟いてね。
Please! Tweet a lot with the hashtag #きゅるるん大作戦DAY1.
っていうか、その前にこれやらないと。あのね、生バンドがね、すごいかっこいいじゃない。
Actually, before that, we have to do this. You know, the live band is really cool, right?
だからちょっと聴かせたくて、じゃあぺこらちゃんから言ってもらっていいですか？
So I wanted to let you hear them. Pekora-chan, could you start us off?
了解！エアバンドキーボード担当、兎田ぺこら！
Roger! Air band keyboard, Usada Pekora!
おーすげー！すごい、めっちゃ弾いてる！
Oh, awesome! Amazing, he's really playing!
よし、行くよ！ギター、宝鐘マリン！
Alright, here I go! Guitar, Houshou Marine!
おーカッケー！かっこいい、かっこいい！
Oh, cool! So cool, so cool!
はい、え、ドラム、白銀ノエル！
Okay, um, drums, Shirogane Noel!
やばい、かっこよ！じゃあ、フレア、ベースやります！
Crazy, so cool! Then, Flare will do the bass!
おーかっけー！かっこいい！かっこいいわ！
Oh, cool! Cool! It's cool!
最高！サンキュー！はい、私たちが演奏してます！
The best! Thank you! Yes, we are performing!
あ、じゃあそろそろ次の曲行きましょうか。
Ah, then let's move on to the next song soon.
あ、ちょっと場所、場所、場所！あ、こっちじゃない、あ、ここでね、ここでね。
Ah, wait, positions, positions, positions! Oh, not this way, ah, here, here.
はい、じゃあそろそろ次の曲行きましょう！せーの！リアリティ・ファンタジー！
Alright, then let's get to the next song! One, two! Reality Fantasy!
冒険 出発 さあ 挑戦 開始 さあ
Adventure! Departure! Now! Challenge! Start! Now!
お宝探しに大海原へ出航だ
Setting sail for the great ocean to find treasure
冒険！出発！さあ！挑戦！開始！さあ！
Adventure! Let's go! Now! Challenge! Start! Now!
身も心もぴょんぴょん ワクワクしちゃって上々
Body and soul are jumping, feeling excited and great
冒険！出発！さあ！挑戦！開始！さあ！
Adventure! Let's go! Now! Challenge! Start! Now!
水平線 向こう側 新天地待っててね
The horizon, the other side, wait for me, new world
運命なんか飛び越してその先へ
Jump over fate and go beyond
さあ リアリティ ファンタジー 二つの狭間へ
Now, to the gap between reality and fantasy
夢歌え 越えた柵一緒に
Sing your dreams, across the fence together
さあ まだ見ぬ世界へと君を連れてくよ
Now, I'll take you to a world you haven't seen yet
みんなが繋がる物語 さあ始まるよ
The story where everyone connects, now it's starting
冒険！出発！さあ！挑戦！開始！さあ！
Adventure! Let's go! Now! Challenge! Start! Now!
みんなの志 抱きいざ騎士団集合
Gather the knights, holding everyone's ambitions
冒険！出発！さあ！挑戦！開始！さあ！
Adventure! Let's go! Now! Challenge! Start! Now!
胸に宿る太陽 風を切ってさらに輝け
The sun in your heart, cut through the wind and shine even more
冒険！出発！さあ！挑戦！開始！さあ！
Adventure! Let's go! Now! Challenge! Start! Now!
名声と夢 晴天に掲げたら突撃だ
Raise your fame and dreams to the clear sky and charge
よってらっしゃい この旅見守って
Come one, come all, watch over this journey
さあ リアリティ ファンタジー 二つの狭間へ
Now, to the gap between reality and fantasy
帆をあげて 目指せユートピアへ
Raise the sails, aim for Utopia
さあ それぞれの世界から 垣根を越えたら
From each of our worlds, if we cross the fence
みんなが繋がる物語 さあ始まるよ
The story where everyone connects, now it's starting
明るく陽気に新たに乗り越え ホロライブ！
Brightly and cheerfully, overcoming anew, Hololive!
愛嬌開放 兎耳澄まして ホロライブ！
Release the charm, prick up the rabbit ears, Hololive!
騎士道と誇り 胸に刻んだら ホロライブ！
Knights' path and pride, carved into the chest, Hololive!
神話に伝わる 神秘の囁き ホロライブ！
Mysterious whispers told in myths, Hololive!
冒険！出発！さあ！挑戦！開始！さあ！
Adventure! Let's go! Now! Challenge! Start! Now!
さあ リアリティ ファンタジー 二つの狭間へ
Now, to the gap between reality and fantasy
夢歌え 越えた柵一緒に
Sing your dreams, across the fence together
さあ まだ見ぬ世界へと君を連れてくよ
Now, I'll take you to a world you haven't seen yet
準備はほらできたよ ルートも決まったよ
Look, preparations are done, the route is decided too
みんなが繋がる物語 さあ始まるよ
The story where everyone connects, now it's starting
時は2026年。2回目の3期生ライブ。
The time is 2026. The second 3rd Generation live.
このチャンスを逃してなるものか。
I won't let this chance escape.
今こそ、全人類兎化計画を、遂行する！
Now, I will carry out the Human Rabbitalization Plan!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peak part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!
The sneak peak part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching.